[{"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130916pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "WDT", "RB", "VBD", "PRP", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "DT", "NNP", "IN", "POS", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 16, "question": "The obvious question, I guess following this is, how does the man with his background a couple of gun-related incidents, discharged from the army of a pattern of misconduct, how does he get clearance to enter one of the most secured military bases in America and do what he did?", "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "DT", "VBZ", ",", "WRB", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "NNS", ",", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", ",", "WRB", "VBZ", "PRP", "VB", "NN", "TO", "VB", "CD", "IN", "DT", "RBS", "VBN", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "NNP", "CC", "VB", "WP", "PRP", "VBD", "."], "aSentId": 17, "answer": "He had a pass that apparently allowed him to enter the day the Yard that's right behind me.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130916pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "VBD", "RB", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 35, "question": "Now, there are 3,000 people who work at the base, how secure is it would you say?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", ",", "EX", "VBP", "CD", "NNS", "WP", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "WRB", "NN", "VBZ", "PRP", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 36, "answer": "Well, I thought the base was very secured.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130916pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "qSentId": 39, "question": "I'm told there are armed security guards, armed police that the civilians that worked there are not allowed to carry a gun, is that correct?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "EX", "VBP", "VBN", "NN", "NNS", ",", "VBN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "WDT", "VBD", "RB", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "IN", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 40, "answer": "Yeah.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130916pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "EX", "VBP", "NN", "NNS", "VBP", "DT", "VBG", ",", "IN", "DT", "NNS", ",", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "JJR", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 42, "question": "Are you aware of their presence?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 43, "answer": "Yeah, there are security guards inside the building, outside the buildings, around the building as you enter the gate.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130916pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "IN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 49, "question": "But he was carrying an AR- 15 assault rifle, another rifle and a handgun, would somebody carrying weapons in the way that he was immediately ring alarm bells inside the base?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "DT", "JJ", "CD", "NN", "NN", ",", "DT", "NN", "CC", "DT", "NN", ",", "MD", "VB", "VBG", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VBG", "NN", "NNS", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 50, "answer": "Well, I don't know how he was able to get in on the base.", "question_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["15"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130916pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "DT", "NN", ",", "VBZ", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "PRP$", "NN", ":", "NN", ":", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 55, "question": "Because presumably -- presumably Patricia, you have to go through some kind of security check to get inside the building?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "RB", ":", "RB", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "RP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "NN", "TO", "VB", "JJ", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 56, "answer": "When you come inside the gate, yes, you have to show your cache (ph) card.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Patricia"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130916pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "DT", "NN", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 59, "question": "Do you need to go through metal detectors?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "RP", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 60, "answer": "No, we don't have any metal detectors.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130916pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 66, "question": "Are you going back to work Patricia tomorrow?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBG", "RB", "TO", "VB", "NNP", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 67, "answer": "No, I will not.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Patricia"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130916pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 70, "question": "What is your feeling towards the man that put you through this and so many of your colleagues?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "NNS", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "CC", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "PRP$", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 71, "answer": "I'm terrified.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130916pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "RB", "VBZ", "RB", "VBG", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 84, "question": "On the one hand, he seems quite shy and very well-behaved, never caused any trouble, on the other, a little clue here and there incidents involving firearms, misconduct later being discharged from the Navy, who is the real Aaron Alexis?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "CD", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "CC", "RB", "JJ", ",", "RB", "VBN", "DT", "NN", ",", "IN", "DT", "JJ", ",", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "RB", "CC", "EX", "NNS", "VBG", "NNS", ",", "NN", "JJ", "VBG", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", ",", "WP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 85, "answer": "That picture really is just emerging Piers.", "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Navy"], "PERSON": ["Aaron Alexis"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130916pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 100, "question": "How could somebody like this with this background just walk on to a base, on to the tip like this, and get inside and be in a position to kill all these people?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "MD", "VB", "IN", "DT", "IN", "DT", "NN", "RB", "VBP", "IN", "TO", "DT", "NN", ",", "IN", "TO", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", ",", "CC", "VB", "JJ", "CC", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "TO", "VB", "DT", "DT", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 101, "answer": "Oh, yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130916pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 123, "question": "Tell me, what prompted you to react like that and expand on what you were saying?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", ",", "WP", "VBN", "PRP", "TO", "VB", "IN", "DT", "CC", "NN", "IN", "WP", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 124, "answer": "Well, you know, Piers, I'm a doctor.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130916pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "RB", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 162, "question": "How many of you been treating the way you are and what is the current set of their condition?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "VBN", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "CC", "WP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 163, "answer": "Sure, I'd be happy to tell you.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130916pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "NN", "RB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 184, "question": "Shawn Henry, in terms of the investigation and from all that you gleaned to date, are we dealing, do you think definitely with a long shooter here?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNP", ",", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "CC", "IN", "DT", "DT", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "NN", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "RB", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 185, "answer": "I don't know that you can make the determination right now.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Shawn Henry"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130916pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "IN", "POS", "RB", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 190, "question": "It did some sort of old state of affairs that the FBI seeking information after the shooter is dead, what do you make of that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "WDT", "DT", "NNP", "VBG", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "JJ", ",", "WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 191, "answer": "I think that that's actually the right protocol.", "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["FBI"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130916pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "JJ", "RB", "WRB", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "TO", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "WP", "PRP$", "NN", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 197, "question": "And are you even more surprised as I am that he's able to walk fully armed into a base of his nature and do what he did?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBP", "PRP", "RB", "RBR", "VBN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "RB", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "CC", "VBP", "WP", "PRP", "VBD", "."], "aSentId": 198, "answer": "ENRY: Well, I don't know that it's clear right now how he actually got the weapons on to the base whether he was in some type of the work track; I'm not clear on what his access was.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["DC"]}, "docId": "130916pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "VBD", "IN", "NNP", ",", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "IN", "NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "TO", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 216, "question": "How on earth do you justify that tweet?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 217, "answer": "Well look at DC, first of all in DC you're not allowed to own any semiautomatic rifle.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130916pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 220, "question": "Where did he buy the M-15?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 221, "answer": "Well, we don't know where he bought it.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Ben"]}, "docId": "130916pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 228, "question": "Do you know that he bought it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 229, "answer": "Because I'm telling a fact Ben.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Piers"]}, "docId": "130916pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "EX", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "RB", ",", "NNP", ",", "WRB", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "TO", "RB", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 250, "question": "Why do you think that's not a problem here?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "POS", "RB", "DT", "NN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 251, "answer": "Well, there is a problem here, Piers, when our failure as a nation is to even talk about the complexity of the problem.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130916pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 266, "question": "Is that right?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 267, "answer": "On this case.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130916pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "NNS", "NNS", "VBP", "VBN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "PRP$", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 278, "question": "You are saying they are inventing those statistics?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "DT", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 279, "answer": "I'm saying multiple people have said that they're wrong in terms of their numbers.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130916pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "DT", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 282, "question": "Is that what your opposition?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "WP", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 283, "answer": "OTT: No, I didn't say they didn't happen.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["2006"]}, "docId": "130916pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", ",", "CD", "VBP", "VBN", "IN", "CD", "."], "qSentId": 299, "question": "Is there -- Is it really necessary?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "EX", ":", "NNP", "PRP", "RB", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 300, "answer": "Of those, 30 have happened since 2006.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Northeastern University"]}, "docId": "130916pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", ":", "NNP", "NNP", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "NNS", "VBP", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "CC", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "TO", "VB", "JJ", "RB", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 304, "question": "What does make them wrong John Lott?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "VB", "PRP", "JJ", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 305, "answer": "You can -- Professor Fox at Northeastern University, others have looked at this and they would warn you to be careful not to use those numbers.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["John Lott"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130916pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 370, "question": "Can it be as simple as that or are we talking about somebody with an underlying serious mental health issue?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "CC", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "IN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "VBG", "JJ", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 371, "answer": "It might be as simple as that.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130916pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 388, "question": "Could that in any way had been partly had trigger for what happened?", "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "DT", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBD", "VBN", "RB", "VBD", "JJR", "IN", "WP", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 389, "answer": "Absolutely.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130916pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 407, "question": "But anger manifested into violence by a gun?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "JJR", "VBN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 408, "answer": "Absolutely.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130916pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "TO", "RB", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "CC", "VB", "VBP", "RB", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "EX", "."], "qSentId": 411, "question": "What's the answer?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 412, "answer": "Well, I think the answer is to really takes a look at these cases and see are there common threads in there.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["November 5th 2009"]}, "docId": "130916pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "RB", "VBZ", "CD", "NN", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "TO", "PRP", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "NNP", "CD", "CD", "."], "qSentId": 423, "question": "What is your reaction?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 424, "answer": "Well, here is one thing it was shocking to me and it go back a lot of memories from November 5th 2009.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130916pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "RB", "RB", ",", "NN", "PRP", "VBZ", "IN", "EX", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", ",", "CC", "EX", "VBZ", "NN", "CC", "EX", "VBZ", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 428, "question": "If you can't even get those kind of things in any kind of sensible gun control legislation what hope is there?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "RB", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "NN", "WP", "NN", "VBZ", "EX", "."], "aSentId": 429, "answer": "Well, right now, today it appears that there is no hope, but there is hope and there's light at the end of tunnel.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Piers"]}, "docId": "130916pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "PRP", "VBP", "CD", "IN", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "IN", ",", "NNP", "VBZ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "JJ", "NNS", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "CC", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 436, "question": "It is the preferred mass shooters weapon of choice, and yet I don't see any logical reason and you're a military man why any civilian needs to have one of these killing machines?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "VBN", "NN", "NNS", "IN", "IN", "NN", ",", "CC", "RB", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "WRB", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "TO", "VB", "CD", "IN", "DT", "VBG", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 437, "answer": "Well, a lot of civilians they purchase one because what you have to look at, Piers is that a lot of times different fractions glorify in AR15 or in automatic rifle.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}]